Once upon a time, a witch laid a curse, which cast a princess into an eternal slumber.
One day, a young man appeared, intending to awake her.
But then, a voice whispers,
Awaken the princess from her sleep! What a cruel thing to do!
For what if the princess wishes not to receive the kiss of awakening,
but rather to continue to sleep forever?
So, you're awake.
Fakir.
What is it?
I wonder what it is I think of you, Fakir.
When I think of Rue, when I think of you, Fakir, and when I'm thinking about Princess
2-2, each one makes me feel different, but I don't know what names I should give these
feelings.
Tell me, Fakir, don't I need to know what they are?
Stop brooding on nonsense.
But...
You listen to me.
You useless, good for nothing.
What's this?
You're trembling.
I just couldn't sleep somehow.
I saw Mewtwo smile.
I guess for Rue, at least, he'll smile like that.
There's no way that Mewtwo doesn't need a heart.
Mewtwo?
I'll get your heart back for you.
Fakir!
Just what is he plotting?
Tricking Mewtwo into obeying him?
Or is it something else completely?
Whatever you're plotting, it's no use.
Princess 2-2 will get all of Mewtwo's hearted.
Ah!
The theater troupe!
Say, it's the Alekid troupe.
Never heard of them.
Sleeping Beauty, huh?
We are a touring ballet company.
Starting the day after tomorrow, we will be performing Sleeping Beauty at this theater.
Please come and see us.
Today we've received special permission for both the boys and girls to come to the
Lecky Troops rehearsal for observation purposes I hope you take this chance to
get a taste of foreign ballet and use that to help get you off the ground
don't you think so we're stuck don't you think oh yes you're right I don't think
so either you don't think so absolutely right I don't think so at all you so you
go back to your room
Mr. Cat's all depressed now
he may not dance back
hmm you're sad because Mewtwo's not here
oh
do Fakir's actions bother you
huh you said you weren't interested in Fakir
she's a dead age what's wrong with that
it's just wrong you're all a be dovey from you don't argue aren't you
you don't even know your own place how cute
so which one do you really love huh
she loves and felt she's too tiny
love
it's really no no not anything like that
that's quite some energy
uh so
man she's one lucky duck
three timings
I'm Palamoni the leading lady nice to meet you
please accept our deepest thanks for sharing your time with us today
miss
let's dispense with formality
I agree
make yourselves at home
it's finally come the premonition of love
rejoice
I'd like you to meet my husband
nice to meet you
now come right on in
oh so pretty
you're so lucky you got to be held like a princess
I can't breathe
oh duck if all you wanted was to be held
you know I would have held you
hold on one second
electric eels
say hello to our troop leader and electrical guy
troop leader
steady supply
I have to hit it at just the right angle
say was our troop leader really an eel
what come to think of it before we came here
no that can't be right
well it'll save on the power bill
that's true
is Rue Princess Tutu
what's wrong
oh it's nothing
I'm sorry
really
then let's continue
say just watching is boring isn't it
let's see someone else
huh
polymony this is too sudden
what does it matter
I want to see
but certainly
I shall show you the results of my lessons
now are there any volunteers
your chance to earn brownie points
losing won't hurt you
no no no
I can't I can't I can't
it cannot be helped then
I will select someone
miss
you
what do you say
I can't do it
no way no way
there you have it
even she herself says she can't
so let's not force her
please enjoy another student's dance
if you like how perform my skills
I guess it was too sudden
I'm so sorry
no we'll dance
we were wanting to dance
we were
really it's all right
that sure scared me
huh
it's a heart chart
or
was it
we'll have a run through tomorrow
so please come watch
we will gladly
I'm always nervous
when I get up on stage
but I've never felt like this
when I was a child
I saw princess Aurora
and instantly fell in love
even after waking
she still seemed to be in a dream
I wanted to become like that someday
so I've danced the part of Aurora
all this time
but
I began to see that it was no use
no matter how I polished my technique
I simply wasn't born with the same talent
I knew my dream would never come true
but
no matter how depressed I'd been
it had never taken me like this
what's the matter with me?
am I afraid of performing?
hey, Palamoni
yes?
we're making dinner
will you help me?
sure
that smells great
though if we don't beat our troop leader soon
we'll have an outage
the premiere
should we postpone?
there's something on your mind, right?
thanks for worrying about me
but
I don't want to trouble everyone else
don't worry
I can still do it
hmm
would anyone like some gems?
beautiful, precious gems
I didn't know you sold gems, Miss Adol
well
Fakir said Nuto doesn't need a heart
but that can't be right
he's weird
real weird
I mean really
Muto doesn't know how it feels to be in love
even though Roo truly loves him
isn't it sad?
is it sad?
you think so, don't you?
is it sad for Muto?
Roo?
or for you, duck?
what?
I'm not really
anyway
no matter what Fakir does to get in my way
I will get all of Muto's heart back to him
I may not be able to make Muto happy like Roo can
since I'm just a bird
but at least I can do this
huh?
pretty!
the name of this gem is dream
yet who is happier?
a dreamer who lingers
or one who is woken?
huh
who would be?
anyway, what's this gem called?
hope
this one?
adventure
and this one?
mystery
okay
what about this?
author's bypass
strange name
okay
in any case
my wish is to get Muto to smile again
and that's all
bye
that's right
I'm going to work harder
and get all the shards of Muto's heart back for him
oh right
go for it
duck
yes
I'll do my best
Muto
yes
go on tomorrow's field trip
I can
and make sure that you ignore what Roo says
yes
I'll be there too
now go to sleep
yes, Fakir
thank you
idiot
you know the girl you called on today
I honestly wanted to see her dance too
she had this glow
sort of a mysterious innate charm, you know
an innate charm
yes
I'm sure
she's pursuing a wonderful dream
and chances are that she's also in love
I can tell
you sure can tell a lot
yeah
because
you were the same when you were younger
you'll always wake from a dream
no
you must wake up
in that case
you shouldn't play Aurora
that was rather blunt
well
the Aurora you've been aspiring to
is the kind of girl who continues to dream
even after she's woken up from her dream, correct?
but you're afraid to even dream
because I can't become that Princess Aurora
sure, there are some dreams that won't come true
but there's no rule that says you can only have one dream
what?
my dream is this
to enthrall people all over the world with your dancing
and to do that
I've even thought of the perfect program for you
perfect for me?
so Palamuni
what do you say to sharing a dream between the two of us?
I had no idea
you really want to do all this?
I haven't woken yet
from my dream or my love
Palo
thank you Palo
I'll dance my final turn as Aurora in this town
yes
and it will be your best
please do not worry
no matter how the wicked witch may curse me
I will surely never prick my finger on a spindle
for though I may dream and dance all my days
I will never lay a hand on a spinning wheel
that smile
was that because he was dancing with me?
or?
our leader's hopeless
alright
everyone
let's take a break
Mr. Cat
huh?
can I help you?
I'd like to speak with you
what?
you'd like to speak with me?
yes
no
you mustn't
oh on this of course you insist
that is in which case
that girl from yesterday
I was hoping you might allow me to watch her dance
oh
I want to see if I can find out
what it is that my performance is lacking
are you sure?
so why'd she pick me?
yes I agree
but someone else would pick me
but I'm really bad at this
yes I know
this is an earnest request from Miss Palamone
don't worry please
dance to your heart's content
even if my dreams of love were to end
because of it I will never
hold that most painful back again
it's been a while since her last pinch
I've waited for this
say Mewto
why don't you partner with her
for the pas des deux
what?
with Mewto?
no
Mewto will stay
I'll go
why?
why did he have to butt in like that?
ooh
our leader's approval gauge is maxed out
Rue
what are you thinking?
pathetic
let me take this chance to make things clear
what?
stay away from Mewto
you stay away from him
you're an eyesore
that's it
this girl's dancing is hardly elegant
but it's overflowing with her own individuality
Mewto's heart
wow
ow
are you alright?
what?
oh yes
I'm sorry for forcing you
you did great
are you hurt?
no
I feel fine
where's the bathroom?
just go out those doors
turn left
and they're at the end of the hall
thank you
she's very sick of us
huh
oh
uh-oh
is the prince's heart running away now?
I wonder what it could be so afraid of
princess Tutu?
please wait
why do you run away?
now let me bring you back to where you belong
I won't
I'm scared
no
you have to
but why?
you just do
what for?
so Mewto can smile
I can take you back
now
come here
no
now
go back
return to Mewto
Mewto
a shard's been returned
what?
everyone
please
stay calm
what?
hang on Mewto
damn that princess Tewtwo
I'm afraid
of princess Tewtwo
Tewtwo
I'm afraid
what?
that can't be
here
on Mewto
uncertainty
get another shot
shard has been returned
but that can't be
that can't be
here
uncertainty
yet another shard
has been returned
but the prince seems rather sad
I wonder what's going to come of this little incident
Stunden
he-he-he-heh
he-heh
it
yet another shard has been returned
but the prince seems rather sad
he-he-heh
I wonder what's going to come of this little incident
he-he
his
the prince seems rather sad
I wonder what's going to come of this little incident
Why this? It just returned a shard of his heart.
Why was Mew Toh crying?
Why was he suffering in such pain?
What's going to happen to him?
I didn't...
I just wanted Mew Toh to smile.
That's all I wanted.
Was it bad?
Was it wrong to want that?
Have I just done something terrible to Mew Toh?
That's right.
This is how the story moves along.
In a direction most undesirable for all concerned parties.
It's weird.
It's kind of scary.
It's good.
The base country comes back.
It's wonderful.
I can't Swami.
He's never as serious.
This is how the story move works.
Being Princess Tutu is meaningless.
The only one I've ever had eyes for is Mewto.
I'm still far from having loved him enough.
I promise to never appear before you again, so don't worry.
These are the feelings of loneliness and of sorrow.
Who are you?
Princess Crayhee.
I see. So you've finally made an appearance.
I will give you nothing. I will let you do nothing.
All who love stories gather round.
First rule, second rule.
Felords carton?
After some time passing a rewrite of Johannes Merrybling.
And if you want to make a list,